<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<!--MovieInfo-->
<Movies>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Noah</Title>
    <Length>138 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>In a world ravaged by human sin, Noah is given a divine mission: to build an Ark to save creation from the coming flood.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Adventure</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Russell Crowe, Emma Watson, Logan Lerman, Jennifer Connelly, Anthony Hopkins, Kevin Durand, Douglas Booth, Dakota Goyo, Mark Margolis, Barry Sloane</Actor>
    <Director>Darren Aronofsky</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, March 28, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/noah.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>11:00am</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>2:20pm</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>4:00pm</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>7:00pm</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>9:00pm</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>
    </Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>
    </Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>
    </Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>
    </Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Transcendence</Title>
    <Length>119 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>Dr. Will Caster is the foremost researcher in the field of Artificial Intelligence, working to create a sentient machine that combines the collective intelligence of everything ever known with the full range of human emotions. His highly controversial experiments have made him famous, but they have also made him the prime target of anti-technology extremists who will do whatever it takes to stop him. However, in their attempt to destroy Will, they inadvertently become the catalyst for him to succeed - to be a participant in his own transcendence. For his wife Evelyn and best friend Max Waters, both fellow researchers, the question is not if they can - but if they should. Their worst fears are realized as Will's thirst for knowledge evolves into a seemingly omnipresent quest for power, to what end is unknown. The only thing that is becoming terrifyingly clear is there may be no way to stop him.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Sci-Fi</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Johnny Depp, Morgan Freeman, Kate Mara, Rebecca Hall, Cillian Murphy, Paul Bettany, Clifton Collins Jr., Luce Rains, Wallace Langham</Actor>
    <Director>Wally Pfister</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, April 18, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/trans.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>9:00am</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>11:00am</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>12:00pm</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>1:00pm</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>2:20pm</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>4:00pm</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>5:00pm</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>7:00pm</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>9:00pm</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Neighbors</Title>
    <Length>97 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>A comedy about a young couple suffering from arrested development who are forced to live next to a fraternity house after the birth of their newborn baby.</Synopsis>
    <Description>d</Description>
    <Genre>Comedy</Genre>
    <Rating>R</Rating>
    <Actor>Zac Efron, Dave Franco, Rose Byrne, Seth Rogen, Jake Johnson, Christopher Mintz-Plasse, Lisa Kudrow, Halston Sage, Carla Gallo, Chasty Ballesteros</Actor>
    <Director>Nicholas Stoller</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, May 9, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/neigh.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>
    </Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>
    </Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>
    </Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>
    </Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>
    </Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>
    </Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>
    </Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>
    </Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>
    </Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Captain America: The Winter Soldier</Title>
    <Length>136 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>After the cataclysmic events in New York with The Avengers, Steve Rogers, aka Captain America, living quietly in Washington, D.C. and trying to adjust to the modern world. But when a S.H.I.E.L.D. colleague comes under attack, Steve becomes embroiled in a web of intrigue that threatens to put the world at risk. Joining forces with the Black Widow, Captain America struggles to expose the ever-widening conspiracy while fighting off professional assassins sent to silence him at every turn. When the full scope of the villainous plot is revealed, Captain America and the Black Widow enlist the help of a new ally, the Falcon. However, they soon find themselves up against an unexpected and formidable enemy-the Winter Soldier.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Adventure</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Chris Evans, Scarlett Johansson, Sebastian Stan, Anthony Mackie, Cobie Smulders, Frank Grillo, Emily VanCamp, Hayley Atwell, Robert Redford, Samuel L. Jackson</Actor>
    <Director>Joe Russo, Anthony Russo</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, April 4, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/Cap-2-banner.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>9:00am</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>11:00am</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>12:00pm</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>1:30pm</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>3:00pm</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>4:00pm</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>5:00pm</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>8:00pm</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>9:00pm</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Neighbors</Title>
    <Length>97 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>A comedy about a young couple suffering from arrested development who are forced to live next to a fraternity house after the birth of their newborn baby.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Comedy</Genre>
    <Rating>R</Rating>
    <Actor>Zac Efron, Dave Franco, Rose Byrne, Seth Rogen, Jake Johnson, Christopher Mintz-Plasse, Lisa Kudrow, Halston Sage, Carla Gallo, Chasty Ballesteros</Actor>
    <Director>Nicholas Stoller</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>05/09/2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>openFileDialog1</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>
    </Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>
    </Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>
    </Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>
    </Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>
    </Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>
    </Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>
    </Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>
    </Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>
    </Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Rio 2</Title>
    <Length>100 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>It's a jungle out there for Blu, Jewel and their three kids in RIO 2, after they're hurtled from that magical city to the wilds of the Amazon. As Blu tries to fit in, he goes beak-to-beak with the vengeful Nigel, and meets the most fearsome adversary of all - his father-in-law.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Family</Genre>
    <Rating>G</Rating>
    <Actor>Jesse Eisenberg, Anne Hathaway, Jemaine Clement, Bruno Mars, Jamie Foxx, Miguel Ferrer, Bebel Gilberto, Jeffrey Garcia, Andy Garcia</Actor>
    <Director>Carlos Saldanha</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>04/11/2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>C:\Users\Leslie\Pictures\rio2newposter.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>10:00AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>1:00PM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>4:40PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>7:30PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>10:10PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>
    </Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>
    </Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>
    </Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>
    </Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>The Quiet Ones</Title>
    <Length>98 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>Tucked away in an estate outside of London, Professor Coupland along with a team of university students conduct an "experiment" on Jane Harper, a young girl who harbors unspeakable secrets. What dark forces they uncover are more terrifying than any of them expected.</Synopsis>
    <Description>Horror</Description>
    <Genre>Horror</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Sam Claflin, Jared Harris, Olivia Cooke, Erin Richards, Max Pirkis</Actor>
    <Director>John Pogue</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>04/25/2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>C:\Users\Leslie\Pictures\TheQuietOnes.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>1:55PM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>4:25PM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>7:25PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>9:45PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>11:25PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>
    </Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>
    </Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>
    </Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>
    </Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Divergent</Title>
    <Length>140 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>In a world divided by factions based on virtues, Tris learns she's Divergent and won't fit in. When she discovers a plot to destroy Divergents, Tris and the mysterious Four must find out what makes Divergents dangerous before it's too late.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Action</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Shailene Woodley, Theo James, Kate Winslet, Jai Courtney, Ray Stevenson, Zoe Kravitz, Miles Teller, Tony Goldwyn, Ansel Elgort, Maggie Q, Mekhi Phifer, </Actor>
    <Director>Neil Burger</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>03/21/2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>C:\Users\Leslie\Pictures\divergent_poster.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>10:30AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>12:10PM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>3:20PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>6:30PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>9:20PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>
    </Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>
    </Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>
    </Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>
    </Showtime9>
  </Movie>
</Movies>