<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<!--MovieInfo-->
<Movies>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Noah</Title>
    <Length>138 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>In a world ravaged by human sin, Noah is given a divine mission: to build an Ark to save creation from the coming flood.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Adventure</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Russell Crowe, Emma Watson, Logan Lerman, Jennifer Connelly, Anthony Hopkins, Kevin Durand, Douglas Booth, Dakota Goyo, Mark Margolis, Barry Sloane</Actor>
    <Director>Darren Aronofsky</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, March 28, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/noah.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>11:00AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>02:20PM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>04:00PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>07:00PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>09:00PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>  :</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>  :</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>  :</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>  :</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Transcendence</Title>
    <Length>119 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>Dr. Will Caster is the foremost researcher in the field of Artificial Intelligence, working to create a sentient machine that combines the collective intelligence of everything ever known with the full range of human emotions. His highly controversial experiments have made him famous, but they have also made him the prime target of anti-technology extremists who will do whatever it takes to stop him. However, in their attempt to destroy Will, they inadvertently become the catalyst for him to succeed - to be a participant in his own transcendence. For his wife Evelyn and best friend Max Waters, both fellow researchers, the question is not if they can - but if they should. Their worst fears are realized as Will's thirst for knowledge evolves into a seemingly omnipresent quest for power, to what end is unknown. The only thing that is becoming terrifyingly clear is there may be no way to stop him.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Sci-Fi</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Johnny Depp, Morgan Freeman, Kate Mara, Rebecca Hall, Cillian Murphy, Paul Bettany, Clifton Collins Jr., Luce Rains, Wallace Langham</Actor>
    <Director>Wally Pfister</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, April 18, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/trans.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>09:00AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>11:00AM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>12:00PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>01:00PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>02:20PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>04:00PM</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>05:00PM</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>07:00PM</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>09:00PM</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>The Protector 2</Title>
    <Length>104 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>When the owner of a major elephant camp is murdered, Kham finds himself the number one suspect and on the run from both the police and the deceased's vengeful twin nieces. But luck is on Kham's side when he runs into an Interpol agent sent to Thailand on a secret mission.</Synopsis>
    <Description></Description>
    <Genre>Action</Genre>
    <Rating>R</Rating>
    <Actor>Tony Jaa, RZA, Petchtai Wongkamlao, Jeeja Yanin, Marrese Crump, Yayaing Phongam, Kazo Patrick Tang</Actor>
    <Director>Prachya Pinkaew</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, May 9, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/theprotector_019.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1></Showtime1>
    <Showtime2></Showtime2>
    <Showtime3></Showtime3>
    <Showtime4></Showtime4>
    <Showtime5></Showtime5>
    <Showtime6></Showtime6>
    <Showtime7></Showtime7>
    <Showtime8></Showtime8>
    <Showtime9></Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Captain America: The Winter Soldier</Title>
    <Length>136 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>After the cataclysmic events in New York with The Avengers, Steve Rogers, aka Captain America, living quietly in Washington, D.C. and trying to adjust to the modern world. But when a S.H.I.E.L.D. colleague comes under attack, Steve becomes embroiled in a web of intrigue that threatens to put the world at risk. Joining forces with the Black Widow, Captain America struggles to expose the ever-widening conspiracy while fighting off professional assassins sent to silence him at every turn. When the full scope of the villainous plot is revealed, Captain America and the Black Widow enlist the help of a new ally, the Falcon. However, they soon find themselves up against an unexpected and formidable enemy-the Winter Soldier.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Adventure</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Chris Evans, Scarlett Johansson, Sebastian Stan, Anthony Mackie, Cobie Smulders, Frank Grillo, Emily VanCamp, Hayley Atwell, Robert Redford, Samuel L. Jackson</Actor>
    <Director>Joe Russo, Anthony Russo</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, April 4, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/Cap-2-banner.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>09:00AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>11:00AM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>12:00PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>01:30PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>03:00PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>04:00PM</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>05:00PM</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>08:00PM</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>09:00PM</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Neighbors</Title>
    <Length>97 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>A comedy about a young couple suffering from arrested development who are forced to live next to a fraternity house after the birth of their newborn baby.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Comedy</Genre>
    <Rating>R</Rating>
    <Actor>Zac Efron, Dave Franco, Rose Byrne, Seth Rogen, Jake Johnson, Christopher Mintz-Plasse, Lisa Kudrow, Halston Sage, Carla Gallo, Chasty Ballesteros</Actor>
    <Director>Nicholas Stoller</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, May 9, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/neigh.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>  :</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>  :</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>  :</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>  :</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>  :</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>  :</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>  :</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>  :</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>  :</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Maleficent</Title>
    <Length>98 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>A vindictive fairy is driven to curse an infant princess only to realize the child may be the only one who can restore peace.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Adventure</Genre>
    <Rating>PG</Rating>
    <Actor>Angelina Jolie, Sharlto Copley, Elle Fanning, Sam Riley, Imelda Staunton, Juno Temple, Lesley Manville, Brenton Thwaites, Miranda Richardson</Actor>
    <Director>Robert Stromberg</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, May 30, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/maleficent.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>  :</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>  :</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>  :</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>  :</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>  :</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>  :</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>  :</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>  :</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>  :</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>X-Men: Days of Future Past</Title>
    <Length>130 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>The X-Men send Wolverine to the past in a desperate effort to change history and prevent an event that results in doom for both humans and mutants.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Action</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Hugh Jackman, James McAvoy, Michael Fassbender, Jennifer Lawrence, Nicholas Hoult, Patrick Stewart, Ian McKellen, Ellen Page, Anna Paquin, Halle Berry, Shawn Ashmore, Peter Dinklage</Actor>
    <Director>Bryan Singer</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, May 23, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/xmendofp.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>  :</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>  :</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>  :</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>  :</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>  :</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>  :</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>  :</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>  :</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>  :</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
    <Movie>
    <Title>Godzilla</Title>
    <Length>123 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>The world's most famous monster is pitted against malevolent creatures who, bolstered by humanity's scientific arrogance, threaten our very existence.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Sci-Fi</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Aaron Johnson, Elizabeth Olsen, Bryan Cranston, Ken Watanabe, David Strathairn</Actor>
    <Director>Gareth Edwards</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, May 16, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/godzilla.jpg</PosterPath>
      <Showtime1>  :</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>  :</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>  :</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>  :</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>  :</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>  :</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>  :</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>  :</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>  :</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  </Movie>
    <Movie>
    <Title>A Million Ways to Die in the West</Title>
    <Length>?? min</Length>
    <Synopsis>As a cowardly farmer begins to fall for the mysterious new woman in town, he must put his new-found courage to the test when her husband, a notorious gun-slinger, announces his arrival</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Western</Genre>
    <Rating>R</Rating>
    <Actor>Seth MacFarlane, Charlize Theron, Liam Neeson, Amanda Seyfried, Sarah Silverman, Giovanni Ribisi, Neil Patrick Harris</Actor>
    <Director>Seth MacFarlane</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, May 30, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/amillionways.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>  :</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>  :</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>  :</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>  :</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>  :</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>  :</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>  :</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>  :</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>  :</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Walk Of Shame</Title>
    <Length>95 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>A reporter's dream of becoming a news anchor is compromised after a one-night stand leaves her stranded in downtown L.A. without a phone, car, ID or money - and only 8 hours to make it to the most important job interview of her life.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Comedy</Genre>
    <Rating>R</Rating>
    <Actor>Elizabeth Banks, James Marsden, Gillian Jacobs, Sarah Wright, Ethan Suplee, Bill Burr, Ken Davitian, Lawrence Gilliard Jr., Alphonso McAuley, Da'Vone McDonld, Eric Etebari, Oliver Hudson</Actor>
    <Director>Steven Brill</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, May 2, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/walkofshame.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>  9:00AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>  11:30AM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>  2:00PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>  4:30PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>  7:00PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>  9:30PM</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>  :</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>  :</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>  :</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Rio 2</Title>
    <Length>100 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>It's a jungle out there for Blu, Jewel and their three kids in RIO 2, after they're hurtled from that magical city to the wilds of the Amazon. As Blu tries to fit in, he goes beak-to-beak with the vengeful Nigel, and meets the most fearsome adversary of all - his father-in-law.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Family</Genre>
    <Rating>G</Rating>
    <Actor>Jesse Eisenberg, Anne Hathaway, Jemaine Clement, Bruno Mars, Jamie Foxx, Miguel Ferrer, Bebel Gilberto, Jeffrey Garcia, Andy Garcia</Actor>
    <Director>Carlos Saldanha</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, April 11, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/rio2newposter.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>10:00AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2> 1:00PM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3> 4:40PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4> 7:30PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>10:10PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>  :</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>  :</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>  :</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>  :</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>The Quiet Ones</Title>
    <Length>98 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>Tucked away in an estate outside of London, Professor Coupland along with a team of university students conduct an "experiment" on Jane Harper, a young girl who harbors unspeakable secrets. What dark forces they uncover are more terrifying than any of them expected.</Synopsis>
    <Description>Horror</Description>
    <Genre>Horror</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Sam Claflin, Jared Harris, Olivia Cooke, Erin Richards, Max Pirkis</Actor>
    <Director>John Pogue</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, April 25, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/TheQuietOnes.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1> 1:55AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2> 4:25PM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3> 7:25PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4> 8:30PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5> 9:45PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>10:00PM</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>11:25PM</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>  :</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>  :</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Divergent</Title>
    <Length>140 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>In a world divided by factions based on virtues, Tris learns she's Divergent and won't fit in. When she discovers a plot to destroy Divergents, Tris and the mysterious Four must find out what makes Divergents dangerous before it's too late.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Action</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Shailene Woodley, Theo James, Kate Winslet, Jai Courtney, Ray Stevenson, Zoe Kravitz, Miles Teller, Tony Goldwyn, Ansel Elgort, Maggie Q, Mekhi Phifer, </Actor>
    <Director>Neil Burger</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, March 21, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/divergent_poster.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>10:30AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>12:10PM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3> 3:20PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4> 5:30PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5> 6:20PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6> 8:15PM</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7> 9:20PM</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>  :</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>  :</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>A Haunted House 2</Title>
    <Length>87 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>Crossing new lines and breaking old barriers, this is the sequel to the hilarious box-office hit starring Marlon Wayans as Malcolm who, after exorcising the demons of his ex, is starting fresh with his new girlfriend and her two children. After moving into their dream home, Malcolm is once again plagued by bizarre paranormal events. With spine-tingling tension and hilarious punch-lines this film is inspired by the latest supernatural horror movie franchises and shows that this time...it's not just the house that's haunted!</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Comedy</Genre>
    <Rating>R</Rating>
    <Actor>Marlon Wayans, Gabriel Iglesias, Affion Crockett, Dave Sheridan, Jaime Pressly, Ricky Overton, Missi Pyle, Ashely Rickards, Rick Overton, Hayes MacArthhur</Actor>
    <Director>Michael Tiddes</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, April 18, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/hauntedhouse2.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>12:20PM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2> 2:00PM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3> 2:40PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4> 4:30PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5> 5:20PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6> 7:10PM</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7> 8:00PM</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8> 9:40PM</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>10:30PM</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>The Amazing Spider-Man 2</Title>
    <Length>140 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>Peter Parker runs the gauntlet as the mysterious company Oscorp sends up a slew of supervillains against him, impacting on his life.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Action</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Andrew Garfield, Emma Stone, Jamie Foxx, Dane DeHaan, Colm Feore, Sally Field, Embeth Davidtz, Paul Giamattie</Actor>
    <Director>Mark Webb</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, May 2, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/spiderman2.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>9:20</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>11:00</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>14:0</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>23:0</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>32:0</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>51:0</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>60:0</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>84:0</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>10:30</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>The Other Woman</Title>
    <Length>109 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>After discovering her boyfriend is married, Carly soon meets the wife he's been cheating on. And when yet another affair is discovered, all three women team up to plot mutual revenge on the three-timing SOB.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Comedy</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Cameron Diaz, Leslie Mann, Don Johnson, Kate Upton, Taylor Kinney, Nicki Minaj, Kenneth Maharaj, Victor Cruz, Nikolaj Coster, David Thornton, Madison McKinley, Alyshia Ochse</Actor>
    <Director>Nick Cassavetes</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, April 25, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/theotherwoman.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1> 2:00PM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2> 2:30PM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3> 4:40PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4> 5:10PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5> 7:20PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6> 7:50PM</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>10:00PM</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>10:40PM</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>11:10PM</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Draft Day</Title>
    <Length>109 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>At the NFL Draft, general manager Sonny Weaver has the opportunity to rebuild his team when he trades for the number one pick. He must decide what he's willing to sacrifice on a life-changing day for a few hundred young men with NFL dreams.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Sport</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Chris Berman, Dave Donaldson, Patrick St. Esprit, Chi McBride, Mel Kiper, Jon Gruden, Kevin Costner, Deion Sanders, Mike Mayock, Jennifer Garner, Anothony Rizzo, Aaron Goldhammer, Chadwick Boseman, Jordan Harris, Zachary Littlejohn</Actor>
    <Director>Ivan Reitman</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, April 11, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/draftday.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>10:00AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>12:00PM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3> 3:20PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>04:10PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5> 7:45PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>10:00PM</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>  :</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>  :</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>  :</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Bears</Title>
    <Length>78 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>A documentary that follows an Alaskan bear family as its young cubs are taught life's most important lessons.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Documentary</Genre>
    <Rating>G</Rating>
    <Actor>John C. Reilly</Actor>
    <Director>Alastair Fothergill, Keith Scholey</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, 18 April 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/bears.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1> 9:30AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2> 11:30AM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3> 1:30PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4> 3:30PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5> 5:30PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6> 7:30PM</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7> 9:30PM:</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8> :</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9> :</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Heaven Is for Real</Title>
    <Length>99 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>A small-town father must find the courage and conviction to share his son's extraordinary, life-changing experience with the world.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Drama</Genre>
    <Rating>PG</Rating>
    <Actor>Greg Kinnear, Kelly Reilly, Connor Corum, Thomas Haden Church, Margo Martindale, Jacob Vargas, Nancy Sorel, Lane Styles</Actor>
    <Director>Randall Wallace</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, 16 April 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/heavenisforreal.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1> 9:00AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2> 11:30AM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3> 2:00PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4> 4:30PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5> 7:00PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6> 9:30PM</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7> </Showtime7>
    <Showtime8> </Showtime8>
    <Showtime9> </Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Brick Mansions</Title>
    <Length>90 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>An undercover Detroit cop navigates a dangerous neighborhood that's surrounded by a containment wall with the help of an ex-con in order to bring down a crime lord and his plot to devastate the entire city.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Action</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Paul Walker, David Belle, RZA</Actor>
    <Director>Camille Delamarre</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, April 25, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/brickmansions.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1> 9:00AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2> 11:00AM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3> 1:00PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4> 3:00PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5> 5:00PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6> 7:00PM</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7> 9:00PM</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8> 11:00PM</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9> </Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Cesar Chavez</Title>
    <Length>102 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>A biography of the civil-rights activist and labor organizer Cesar Chavez.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Biography</Genre>
    <Rating>PG-13</Rating>
    <Actor>Michael Peña, America Ferrera, Rosario Dawson, John Malkovich</Actor>
    <Director>Diego Luna</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, March 28, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/cesarchavez.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1> 9:15AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2> 11:20AM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3> 2:10pM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4> 4:45PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5> </Showtime5>
    <Showtime6> </Showtime6>
    <Showtime7> </Showtime7>
    <Showtime8> </Showtime8>
    <Showtime9> </Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Bad Words</Title>
    <Length>89 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>A spelling bee loser sets out to exact revenge by finding a loophole and attempting to win as an adult.</Synopsis>
    <Description></Description>
    <Genre>Comedy</Genre>
    <Rating>R</Rating>
    <Actor>Jason Bateman, Kathryn Hahn, Philip Baker Hall, Allison Janney, Ben Falcone</Actor>
    <Director>Jason Bateman</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, March 14, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/badwords.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1> 10:00AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2> 12:00PM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3> 2:00PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4> 4:00PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5> 6:00PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6> 8:00PM</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7></Showtime7>
    <Showtime8></Showtime8>
    <Showtime9></Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Mr. Peabody & Sherman</Title>
    <Length>92 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>The time-travelling adventures of an advanced canine and his adopted son, as they endeavor to fix a time rift they created.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Animation</Genre>
    <Rating>PG</Rating>
    <Actor>Ty Burrell, Stephen Colbert, Ariel Winter, Patrick Warburton, Stanley Tucci, Lake Bell, Leslie Mann, Mel Brooks, Allison Janney</Actor>
    <Director>Rob Minkoff</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, March 28, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/mrpeabodyandsherman.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1> 9:45AM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2> 12:30PM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3> 3:05PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4> 5:45PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5> </Showtime5>
    <Showtime6> </Showtime6>
    <Showtime7> </Showtime7>
    <Showtime8> </Showtime8>
    <Showtime9> </Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>300: Rise of An Empire</Title>
    <Length>102 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>Greek general Themistokles leads the charge against invading Persian forces led by mortal-turned-god Xerxes and Artemisia, vengeful commander of the Persian navy.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Action</Genre>
    <Rating>R</Rating>
    <Actor>Sullivan Stapleton, Eva Green, Lena Headey, Rodrigo Santoro, Jack O'Connell, David Wenham</Actor>
    <Director>Noam Murro</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, March 7, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/300rise.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1> 12:00PM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2> 2:20PM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3> 4:45PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4> 7:00PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5> 9:15PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6> </Showtime6>
    <Showtime7> </Showtime7>
    <Showtime8> </Showtime8>
    <Showtime9> </Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Oculus</Title>
    <Length>104 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>A woman tries to exonerate her brother, who was convicted of murder, by proving that the crime was committed by a supernatural phenomenon.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Horror</Genre>
    <Rating>R</Rating>
    <Actor>Karen Gillan, Brenton Thwaites, Katee Sackhoff, Rory Cochrane</Actor>
    <Director>Mike Flanagan</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>Friday, April 11, 2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>../../Posters/oculus.jpg</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1> 3:00PM</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2> 5:00PM</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3> 7:00PM</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4> 9:00PM</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5> 11:00PM</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6> </Showtime6>
    <Showtime7> </Showtime7>
    <Showtime8> </Showtime8>
    <Showtime9> </Showtime9>
  </Movie>
  <Movie>
    <Title>Walk Of Shame</Title>
    <Length>95 min</Length>
    <Synopsis>A reporter's dream of becoming a news anchor is compromised after a one-night stand leaves her stranded in downtown L.A. without a phone, car, ID or money - and only 8 hours to make it to the most important job interview of her life.</Synopsis>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Genre>Comedy</Genre>
    <Rating>R</Rating>
    <Actor>Elizabeth Banks, James Marsden, Gillian Jacobs, Sarah Wright, Ethan Suplee, Bill Burr, Ken Davitian, Lawrence Gilliard Jr., Alphonso McAuley, Da'Vone McDonld, Eric Etebari, Oliver Hudson</Actor>
    <Director>Steven Brill</Director>
    <ReleaseDate>05/02/2014</ReleaseDate>
    <PosterPath>openFileDialog1</PosterPath>
    <Showtime1>  :System.Windows.Forms.ComboBox, Items.Count: 2</Showtime1>
    <Showtime2>  :System.Windows.Forms.ComboBox, Items.Count: 2</Showtime2>
    <Showtime3>  :System.Windows.Forms.ComboBox, Items.Count: 2</Showtime3>
    <Showtime4>  :System.Windows.Forms.ComboBox, Items.Count: 2</Showtime4>
    <Showtime5>  :System.Windows.Forms.ComboBox, Items.Count: 2</Showtime5>
    <Showtime6>  :System.Windows.Forms.ComboBox, Items.Count: 2</Showtime6>
    <Showtime7>  :System.Windows.Forms.ComboBox, Items.Count: 2</Showtime7>
    <Showtime8>  :System.Windows.Forms.ComboBox, Items.Count: 2</Showtime8>
    <Showtime9>  :System.Windows.Forms.ComboBox, Items.Count: 2</Showtime9>
  </Movie>
</Movies>